

"DWIC is never enough!"

Summary

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, language model and vision-language grounding. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience ____

CSE, UNSW Sydney, Australia

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY Lizhen Qu AND Lina Yao

Feb. 2021 - Present

• Self-proposed research project: Visual Commonsense Reasoning in Complex Events Detection

Harrison.ai Sydney, Australia

APPLIED AI SCIENTIST INTERN, SUPERVISED BY Ben Hachey

• Develop AI algorithms, prototypes and solutions for Prioritization of patients' CT Brain reports.

Linked entity fuzzy search via sense2vec + SciSpacy + stanza + FastText

Contextual word semantic search via domain adaptive DistilBERT in an unsupervised fashion

Mean pooling sentence semantic search via domain adaptive DistilBERT in an unsupervised fashion

Sentence semantic search via BioSentVec + FastText

Sentence semantic search via DistilBERT (with BERT-flow)

Anserini+BM25+RM3+SBERT cross-encoder

Data61, CSIRO Remote

EXTERNAL RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY Conrad Sanderson, WORK WITH Jason Rumenagan

• PyArmadillo, a API library of Armadillo using Python-C++ bindings Write and design under the product development flow with the Data61 vacation scholar.

Open-source minimum viable product(MVP) at the first stage.

Monash Univeristy Remote

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY Reza Haffari AND Lizhen Qu

 Project: Commonsense Reasoning Question Answering Apply ProphetNet as the backbone for the model trained on ATOMIC data.

Evaluate the proposed model results.

Co-authored a long paper accepted by COLING 2020.

Co-authored a short paper submitted ACL 2021.

• Project: Construction of a Multimodal Procedural Knowledge Base for Action Planning

Design and collect crowdsourcing data via Amazon Mechanical Turk.

Design the baseline and propose a multimodal action planning model via the knowledge base.

A long paper for ICCV 2021 is under preparation.

UNSW Sydney Sydney, Australia

• **ENGG1000**: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation:

20T1, 20T3(100% student satisfaction), 21T1

• ELEC2134: Circuits and Signals:

The only undergraduate in the team while remains are PhDs. 20T1, 20T3, 21T1

• **COMP1010**: The Art of Computing:

21T1(Backup)

• COMP2521: Data Structures and Algorithms:

21T1

CASUAL ACADEMIC/TUTOR

• **COMP9020**: Foundations of Computer Science* (**Graduate Course**):

21T1

• **COMP9021**: Principles of Programming* (**Graduate Course**):

• COMP9024: Data Structures and Algorithms* (Graduate Course):

21T1

Dec, 2020 - Present

May, 2020 - Present

Dec, 2020 - Feb, 2021

Feb, 2020 - Present

Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia Nov, 2019 - Sep, 2020

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY Arne Laucht

- Propose a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- · Propose the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec, 2019 - Feb, 2020

- Apply Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- Design cloud architecture for top tier companies.

Project

PyArmadillo Data61

CO-LEAD DEVELOPER Dec, 2020 - Present

- Design and develop the Cube class in PyArmadillo.
- Validate the performance of the library.
- Write the user document.
- Design the tests.

Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

 RESEARCHER
 Feb, 2020 - Dec, 2020

- Determine the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- · Research existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Github

Contributor, Collaborator May, 2020 - Present

• Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

Sphinx Markdown Builder Github

Contributor May, 2020 - Present

• Sphinx builder that outputs markdown files.

Education

UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)

Sydney, Australia

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - Sep. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 86.3, Top 3% in Faculty of Engineering

Extracurricular Activity ____

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

POWER ENGINEER Oct, 2019 - Dec, 2020

- Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.
- Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

ELSOC UNSW UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

Publication

PyArmadillo: an alternative approach to linear algebra in Python

Journal of Open Source Software

JASON RUMENGAN, TERRY YUE ZHUO, CONRAD SANDERSON

In Prepartion

Neural Symbolic Commonsense Reasoner with Relation Predictors

ACL 2021

SUBMITTED TO ACL 2021 In Submission

JANUARY 31, 2021 TERRY YUE ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ 2

COSMO: Conditional SEQ2SEQ-based Mixture Model for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering

COLING 2020

Farhad Moghimifar, Lizhen Qu, **Yue Zhuo**, Mahsa Baktashmotlagh and Gholamreza Haffari

Oct, 2020

Honors & Awards

2019	Dean's Honours List (Highly Commended), Top 2% of UNSW Engineering	Sydney
2019	Taste of Research scholarships Recipient (A\$5,000), TOP 12 of UNSW Engineering	Sydney
2020	Taste of Research scholarships Recipient (A\$6,000), TOP 43 of UNSW Engineering	Sydney

Service _____

2021	Volunteer, AAAI 2021	Online
2020	Volunteer, EMNLP 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, NeurIPS 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, WiNLP 2020	Seattle, WA